No one else did. This is your work.
You're supposed to get this orientation.
Yes, I I I didn't do the documentation.
I didn't do the walkthrough, right? Yes,
yeah, yes.
Who will have to tell? I don't know. No,
we had no time. I tried my best, but this,
I was telling Ali,
now we're really getting into not
documented territory.
We're gonna use the visual for discussion
purposes,
but I don't think we'll roll a lot of
this stuff down.
And so, we'll see,
and I think we'll need the next session
for it as well. We'll record it.
I'll try to backfill the documentation,
but I don't think I can do it 'cause I
don't know some of the nuances of like
the deficiencies is with you,
so I think I need your help with that,
but we can we can talk to it,
trying to back in some feature issue.
So, but what I thought,
and then you let me know if this is
useful, because what I was going to do is,
I think you've heard about most of this
stuff already,
but we'll go through kind of like the
what and the why anyway,
as a capability overview. This is,
I guess, my current,
I might be missing some stuff.
But this is my great universe of of what
I define as platform management.
And then so it is a capability map of
platform management. Like I said,
I might be missing details, boxes,
kind of uncover that as we go,
but at least should explain what.
what it is. We'll go through,
like kind of do we need to go through
like questions about how it works, maybe,
like what is it look like today,
how it works. Do the demo, formal demo,
so you're not kind of having to poke
around yourself.
And then we'll talk about what it does do
and what it doesn't do.
I think that's probably the most
important conversation to have,
because I'm not sure if that's going to
be.
easily uncovered on your own.
I'm sure you'll find out at some point.
What? OK.
But it would be nice if you had a bit of
a heads up. Yeah, yeah. OK. So.
There's, did I slice it up? Yeah,
so for me,
like I think there's three main buckets
of capabilities within platform
management.
The actual platform configuration, please,
so setting up the platform to work the
way it should for anybody who's consuming
the platform.
There is then the kind of the set of
people to get access to whatever they
need to do on the platform,
both at the firm and user level.
And then I tagged this on at the end
because it technically is platform
experience,
but we never really kind of fully debated
that one else.
So it's easier if you're looking at
platform configuration from user
management to also look at that
connecting all of this to the user access
journey itself.
So how does a user log in and what do
they see?
So all of that right now, today is under,
I guess,
what Candi and I have been looking at,
like in terms of kind of roadmap
development and product development. So,
I'll start on this end. Mostly,
it was all it was 100% you until I...
Forced my way in 11 months ago,
so where is to have the right, yeah.
So, starting with platform configuration,
this is probably...
Very familiar, hopefully,
because all of our discovery sessions are
about creating this capability,
'cause it doesn't like,
so I forgot we're recording,
I'm gonna point this capability,
because it simply doesn't exist today,
so objective of feature management is to
have.
Obviously,
a representation of product features on
the platform,
so that that that kind of that feature
could be used for anything kind of to the
to the right, right?
So for for downstream application,
ultimately the platform is distribution
of features, that's what it does,
and therefore we need to have a concept
of features like feature management.
And feature management should be the life
cycle of the feature itself.
So from the point of feature creation,
onboarding, registration,
all the way through to deprecation,
when we,
anytime we see the word management,
basically anywhere on this map,
it means the life cycle management of
that thing, right? Okay.
So this is really feature lifecycle
management. How do I register?
How do I deprecate? How do I version?
How do I feature flag?
All of this stuff would be under the
domain of how do I configure feature,
how do I configure the feature and its
behavior on the platform, right?
So this you should be familiar with by
now. I know it's still month one.
by at least all of the discovery sessions
is to actually establish this because you
know that today we don't have the concept
of a feature on the platform, right?
It's a bunch of resources and those
resources unfortunately do a whole whack
load of different things.
It's not just about access, it's about,
you know, presentation in the UI.
We've got resources, like you said,
to federate the access control points.
We've got resources to drive the
configuration. Like this is.
It's a whole mess of a deal,
and so to be able to abstract the concept
of what is an actual feature,
that's what we're working on right now,
right? Then we have permission management,
which is different to feature management.
We need a, we need a role,
we need a permission model.
We have that today.
We talked a little bit about this,
but permissions management is how do you
control.
User entitlement specifically,
feature access is one thing,
but entitlements is something different,
right? So the actual scopes of like,
you know, the view, the read, write,
like that stuff goes into here, sorry,
mouse permissions,
and and so the core of our permission
role only does one thing, is really,
it's Okta, it's the role management,
it's our RBAC model.
right,
that sits underneath the feature
management so that the feature plus the
permissions is then applied to firm user
management.
So you need those two components because
one addresses entitlements and the other
addresses the ability for you to
provision features to people.
We just talked about platform integration,
so I don't need to go through this,
but complementing the ability to onboard
a feature,
you physically have to onboard the damn
thing, right? So, the, like, the,
you know, the access, the UX,
which is the session navigation,
and the micro app we just talked about,
so we don't need to get into that,
and we'll...
Again,
I think it is worth us doing the exercise
together of assessing all of our
integrations today to formalize this for
you. But I won't get into this,
but these three things together,
these three capabilities together,
should form the basis of the next step of
the journey,
which is my ability to have all of this.
Apply to a firm or user? Yeah,
just the terms from 'cause JPE manage a
similar hierarchy just to fit in the
cross-reference to business capability,
and we call the permission management
entitlement management.
Yeah,
and it's more precise to the entitlement
management,
just that sometimes we use the term
loosely and differently,
and the different term can mean the same
thing. Yeah, just, you know,
we're really to convince people that
terminology, like, yeah,
what's a module versus a feature?
It's the same thing. What's a feature?
What's an app versus a module?
That's different.
I think it's still a nightmare for me
sometimes happening in this conversations.
He's saying, okay, he used module,
the other thing is stumbling between.
Yeah.
Ultimately,
it's whatever works with the counterparty
you're talking to. We use that terminal.
Yeah, I'm getting used to that.
Well, what's even more confusing,
to Candi's point, right, is, like, yeah,
this probably should say entitlements,
but at the bank, you know,
as with all enterprise architecture,
of course,
enterprise architecture has a vision of
the world, yeah,
which sometimes doesn't fit with product
capability hierarchy,
and product really is.
business capability hierarchy,
but you might hear IT and JP sometimes
say, oh, you know,
this needs to line up to the BCM,
the business capability model.
And more typically we say, okay, JP,
do what you have to do.
You know that when you,
I know this is on record,
I need Kevin to hear this.
You know that when it comes to.
our vision of the world and how we slice
up features and how we divide that
against product. There's a way we do it,
which is against the client journey,
which is against the product line.
It makes sense for us.
It makes sense for our clients.
That's not the way the bank does it.
The bank does it by domains, right?
And sometimes those domains don't fit,
which is where we say,
do what you need to do, JP,
but just don't.
Get bring that world into here,
because even even a simple concept like
our INITIUM model, sorry, sorry,
I need to take something, yeah, but like,
sorry.
Cyquest.
I forgot about the beating up to mention
it.
But his technical, he, he knows, yeah.
Yeah, is a luxury to get them all for me.
Is it? Yeah, it is.
This is all your stuff.
No one ever did that.
Because we were building this. The whole,
like we didn't,
if we started seven years ago,
we don't have this. Yeah,
I was thinking how would we do it
differently if we knew it.
Like, if we can travel back,
start on this side, five years ago,
create the map,
start on this side and work this way,
not the other way around,
'cause we started, remember,
we started on this side and then we work
this way, yeah,
probably it's like crunched, yeah, yeah,
and then whenever they talk about the
framework, the high, high level hierarchy,
whatever, we said, no, no, no,
we want something tangible.
We want something else, too.
So then we didn't get the time to think
about the hierarchy of the framework.
Yeah,
we should have spent all of our time here
modeling this. Like the first year.
We didn't envision that, do we? Yeah,
we did.
This is like our requirements have never
changed.
I can pull up any artifacts from five
years ago.
And we have the concept of feature and
entitlements management.
We have that because we actually modeled
after all the problems with legacy. So,
but this was this was the ask while while
the delivery was focused on login,
we said come up with a model.
We just never came up with one. Yeah.
That was the problem.
I think is I we need to launch something.
Yeah.
Yeah, but even that, sorry,
year one was supposed to be this.
I was very clear with Varun. Like, guys,
we start from there,
we wouldn't have any deliverable for him.
Like, he couldn't, yeah,
but that was fine.
I never asked you guys to do something
first, but it's demonstrable. I said,
start here. Yeah, we we did.
That's where we came out with the Outback.
Yeah, I know. So we defined,
we we do have the feature entitling, yeah,
but the the like the model didn't like
this was the biggest piece of churn,
right? And so,
whilst this was fitting for 11 months,
what are you gonna do while you're gonna
you're gonna do something else,
'cause otherwise the team has no no work,
yeah, I know.
You can't do mine. Of course I do.
Not every day.
And document this is like peeling back
all the scars. We could have,
we should have. We should have. Yeah,
Candi and I were just talking about like
if we were to go back in time,
because this is our five years of work,
is if we were to go back in time,
what would we change? Well,
we would start on the left and work our
way to the right instead of the other way
around.
Because the login was the first
deliverable.
But we kind of said like we wanted the
first year to be spent on a new model,
but we just never got to a point where
everybody agreed.
So we spent the time to build up the mess,
the roles and so on. Yeah,
like this was like a,
this was like a year's worth of like
contemplation. How should we change it?
We know that the legacy model doesn't
work today.
So how do we pivot to something better?
You see in R2, like even Candi brought up,
like,
why do I get this random thing called
transfer in and I check that. Like,
is it part of something or not part of
something?
And then these onboarding profiles, like,
how does it?
Like, how does it work?
And then these firm data specialists,
is that a feature access or a data access?
Like,
it was like the concepts were all kind of
not clear. It wasn't well modeled.
And so we said, okay,
we understand all of that.
We understand the need because we know
our firms at the time and how they were
set up, like all those.
business context, we have all of that,
right?
So how do we model all of that into a
flexible feature and entitlement
management model? That was year one.
Unfortunately, after year one,
there was no result. There was no model.
Like it was just kind of like a, you know,
bank was saying you must do RBAC,
you must do RBAC, and then okay,
we can't retrofit the feature.
concept into RBAC and then there was a
huge philosophical debate about, well,
in BNI and you shouldn't be doing feature
management, you should be doing RBAC.
There was like 12 months of that.
And so that's why you see all the
problems we have today is because this
was partially modeled. And so as a result,
going into now immediately the
conversations with this,
we didn't have a good representation of
features because we only went as far as
at least register the resources,
at least have an inventory of that.
But now the resources.
do a whole bunch of different things,
right?
It defines your entry point on the UI,
it defines access,
it defines configuration, right?
And now we're saying, okay,
let's clean that up and map that to an
actual feature.
So at least we know what the feature is
made of and what resources it has and
what type, like what.
those resources do,
but at that point it wasn't clear.
Like it was like there was no solution
for it.
So we abandoned feature management as a
result of that, which like,
like we just can't sit on this for
another year.
I don't know when you guys are going to
reconcile.
The bank wasn't necessarily changing
their position on our back. Actually,
we found out our architect didn't want to
fight that battle.
So he just kind of said.
just take what the bank has and call it a
day. And then now JP is saying,
why did you guys do that? Right? Like,
you didn't have to go down that strict
one user profile per user discussion.
You could have changed it.
It could have been better supported.
And so you'll hear sometimes the team
talk about 2.0, 2.0, because this was.
Under 1.0,
we're just in resource land and resource
help with no concept of feature.
And then we said after we launched, okay,
this model is not going to work forever
because as you can see,
once we add more and more integration,
this gets more,
the list gets bigger and bigger and it's
very hard to maintain.
Like you need specialized expertise.
to know what the developers interpreted
as resources, right? And you need to pick,
like, what if Paul leaves? Like,
we're totally screwed, right? So,
that's a problem.
It's not abstracted in a way that it's
usable, right? So,
then we said we probably need a much more
flexible model,
and so JP kind of proposed with...
team that we need to move on from this
RBAC into a policy-based model.
And then I kind of said, okay,
that's too big of a jump.
We are going too far.
Let's put the rest of the pieces in first.
Like let's formalize the concept of a
feature.
Let's formalize kind of do we understand
how to properly permission those features.
Do we understand this?
If we fully understand that and it and it
and and we're still hitting limitations,
then you can do maybe like 1.5, right?
Move on to multi-user group.
And then if that also doesn't support,
then you can rip it up and do it again.
Because going from RBAC to policy base is
a huge leap.
And we don't have operational processes
that support that transition today,
because we're still we were at the point
until right before you joined,
we were still very confused about how
this works on the feature on the on the
kind of the platform configuration side,
right?
And so maybe a bit of backstory there,
so at some point...
if you're hitting the limits of this
platform, you might kind of say, okay,
do we need to maybe address the
limitations of the permissioning?
I think this is a pretty severe
limitations.
This is the reason why we have so many
packages. And those packages,
Candi can tell you all about it,
extremely difficult to maintain,
very little transparency.
into the updates and we've had issues
with deployment,
incremental deployment into higher
environments,
because every environment needs to follow
the same steps.
It's updated by script or what have you
not,
and then so somebody can make a mistake
in production. Yeah, right.
So there's kind of problems there,
but I think here.
Candi,
maybe you can actually list them for Ali,
right,
on some of the operational issues that we
have.
So, you might, you might,
you might kind of get into that
specifically to this area.
I think we we talked about we have
twenty-six user packages user packages.
And I want to understand that,
and these user packages are stored inside
Okta.
If I'm not drunk, where,
where are they actually stored?
Compass. Compass. Yeah. How,
how these user packages interaction with
Okta? The other thing is user group, so,
yeah, so in Okta,
how Okta operate is they, they,
they create user groups.
So then in each user group,
if you want someone to have provision to
something,
you will add that person to the user
group. So far,
Canvas is constructed in a way.
We only assign one user group,
one or two user group per person,
but it is actually a self-imposed
restriction. Alpha can support multiple.
So
The same person can be added to multiple
user groups. But anyway,
we decide that way.
One user package would link to or
corresponds to one user group in Alpha.
So if you are assigned to this user
package, manage all.
And then behind the scene,
when you assign it,
the user management would be sending your
request or your ID over to author and you
to whatever we define as the manage or
user group.
So your profile will be assigned to that
door or your assigned to that user group.
But this,
the definition of what's actually in the
user,
the Okta user group is actually different
to a compass user package, right? Because,
like,
in the in the user group definition in
Okta, it would be what,
like a bunch of scopes and what have you
not, and then on the compass side,
it's resources, yes, yes,
so they're not the same thing,
we just happen to match the,
they should be mapped, yeah.
Okay, and it's one-to-one, one person,
one identity, one user group,
one user package.
It's like that, or two, yeah, two, OK.
Now I want to understand whether a firm
user, I mean, Wellington Alliance,
if I'm not right. Wellington Altus, yeah.
Wellington Altus, or someone from...
Inside back comes to the compass X.
Enter the credentials, and then after,
once entering the credentials,
click authenticate,
the message goes directly to Okta.
And Okta authenticates,
authorize based on the that identity and
the credentials says, okay,
this is the number of the user groups,
okay? And then it pass something,
I don't know, whatever.
Maybe we can take it offline.
It's the technical.
Our job.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, just, yeah,
I want to understand the process that is
this the process sequence that I
explained is the is it the right sequence,
the sequence diagram in some of JP's page.
OK,
so we can understand the locking and
stuff, yeah, and it's not different that.
Whether it's an internal bank user or
it's a firm user, for example,
we're all on the external active tenant,
so same active tenant, the request will,
because we all log in the same way from
the external locate experience, yeah,
but then in future when you're coming
from...
In a month's time,
when the employee SSO is done,
then all the employees are going to be
set up in an internal tenant,
which is different from the external
tenant. It's still an Okta instance,
but it's just a different Okta tenant.
Yeah, same sequencing for everything,
but OK, but just the...
Internal segmentation inside of that,
that's right. OK, but...
It's a policy that...
When Compass X has users outside of the
bank.
They should come into Okta.
Okta is a service provider for
COPRESCOCHEF. Yeah.
And is managed by bank, not by... Correct.
Okay.
OK,
do we have we do we still have a like a
how's the relationship with the Octa team
these days?
Ohh, the cam ticket, yeah, C.I.A.M.
tickets, yeah, no,
but like they they typically are decent.
I heard to turn around is quite slow,
yeah.
But not as bad as the ECM team.
So, I think so.
At least I respond, yeah.
Where was I going with this thought
process? You finished this side.
Did I finish this side? So yeah, UAM,
like whatever's in scope of, like,
so going back to feature management in
terms of what it does and what it doesn't
do, you're in the discovery,
so you'll know.
I don't think we're going to get into
this.
Platform integrations will do that
assessment as well,
so you know what we can do and what we
can't do.
And then we just talked about the
permission management.
There's some limitations there.
But I mean,
it like it's a very industry standard
service.
So we use it in a very industry standard
way.
So apart from the RBAC limitation of the
single user group to a single user
identity, like the rest of it is fine.
We don't tend to see a lot of outages,
like thank God,
like it's basically your gateway into
everything.
I think we had one in the last five years.
So it's not too bad.
So I think, yeah,
I think maybe we spend more time in firm
user management side.
To,
and then you know all the packaging
limitations as well, right?
Like that we were kind of going through,
it's...
It's not flexible because it's the
limitation of the RVAC. Otherwise,
we would have just said, like,
kind of each capability has its own kind
of user group and you can be assigned to,
are you in the account opening user group,
are you in the orders user group?
It's a lot easier that way.
And then even add-ons,
like we don't have a good solution for
add-ons. That's why all.
add-on on core services get added to all
the packages.
Not the best way of doing that.
Like that's not,
that's not great from an access control
perspective. It's just,
it just says you like anybody is entitled
to any add-on,
which is not actually correct, right?
It works, but it's not great.
So at some point.
We go to 1.5 multi-user group,
we have a user group for Creases, right?
And that's how you represent your
permission into Creases,
separate to all the other capabilities
that we have.
That would be the 1.5 model,
and then then if.
It needs to be even more flexible than
that, like,
so specific firm threshold
implementations,
like rule-based policies against firms.
If that starts to come through the door,
then the next natural evolution on top of
the 1.5, the multi-user group,
would be the policy-based access control.
But I'm not, I'm not sure,
I'm not sure we have that.
I don't, I just don't,
I don't think you have my use cases for
that today.
I will only tell you this because people
are going to talk to you about feedback
and this is your response. Like, yeah,
I'm not sure if there's a lot of use
cases for that yet.
Yeah.
It's huge.
You're gonna have to refactor the whole
bloody platform. It's huge, right?
So it's gonna be very costly.
Regarding your comment about the
third-party applications, as you say,
it's not interesting to throw them under,
you know,
under features and do not have a...
Right now,
we don't have granular resources.
What's your utopia for?
Because from my understanding is that if
we want to deep dive,
it's like the third tier, like, you know,
like that's integration. Otherwise.
You should let them, okay,
they have their own SAS environment and
we just keep the track of the user.
But yeah, I I don't know where,
where is your utopia with that? Yeah, no,
it's never the, it's never the three,
it's an ecosystem, right? So, to me,
core should be always in the three,
because there's a lot of related things.
If you think about, like,
actually I got this yesterday,
well simple,
because I opened a new checking account
with those, well simple.
Because I was like, I wanna see,
I wanna see, yeah, yeah, and then,
and then it kind of gives you, like,
once you open the account, it gives you,
OK,
there are four things you should do next,
right? You wanna transfer money in,
you wanna deposit, you wanna set up,
I forgot what they direct debit,
is it direct, yeah, direct debit,
and then I took a screenshot,
because I was like, oh,
that's kind of cool.
Yeah, add money, set up direct deposit,
receive e-transfers, add billing, pays,
right?
All of this stuff is done in context of
the app and their integrated functions,
because this is core to the online
banking journey.
You don't want this chef to kind of go
somewhere else,
but when you go into their loyalty
program, the offers that they have,
they send you somewhere else.
Right?
Because it's not a core workflow of the
banking experience.
So we're a banking environment.
It's the same thing.
Like I don't want to like open an account
and go somewhere else to do a transfer
and kind of set up direct deposits.
I want to be in context of the accounting
context of my operational environment to
do that.
The only way to do that is you either
build it yourself or you make the third
party integrate.
in a way that looks like you built it
yourself, right?
That fits into the user flows and you
have control over it.
That's the only time you would ever do a
tier 3. And so outside of the core.
I'm not, I'm not convinced,
like the you can do, and by the way,
I forgot to mention this earlier,
so that's my current definition of the
tiering.
There's probably more tiering in within
the tiers themselves.
You can do a basic SSO and pass minimal
context over,
and that could be an integration because
that standalone does not require that
context at all.
Or let's say you ask about the vision,
right,
is some apps I think deserve context from
Compass.
So if you look at a portfolio management
system, what does it do?
You can view accounts on the portfolio
management system.
You can trade on the portfolio management
system.
You can rebalance and you can allocate.
on the portfolio management system.
I already have context of that as a user.
Why would I not want to try to help the
firm harmonize that?
So if I can do core trading in Compass,
I should be able to trade in the PM
system.
If I can do core allocations on Compass,
I should be able to allocate on the
trading system. I would like for those.
PM systems have that context.
So then they don't have to then kind of
take that user. Okay,
now that user has access,
because we did a basic SSO,
now you got to go in and configure their
profile and manually and set them up.
And then sometimes you set it up and wait,
oh,
this person can trade in the PM system,
but they can't trade here. Why? Right?
Because it's.
completely different setups.
There are some core adjacent stuff that's
tied to the core services.
Maybe you want to pass more context for
that. Like that would be ideal.
Because then the access experience is
consistent in the mind of the user, right?
Yes.
And that's why we keep a global profile.
But we don't do that right now, obviously.
And again, need-wise,
does it work today for those firms that
are on digit or increases? Yeah,
it kind of does.
Do they have issues sometimes? Yeah,
what do they do? They call, we fix it,
we move on, right?
So the overhead of that is not as big as..
.
having like 28 IDs because there's four
platforms and you're accessing them
separately because they're not integrated
and we don't have multi-firm.
That's way worse.
And then you run through an attestation
process for 28 IDs at a time for each
person that exists in the firm and that
firm has 400 users.
Yeah, yeah, um,
but but it would be it would be nice for..
.
core adjacent, right,
things that spin off of the core workflow
for them to be able to take more context
from us.
Yeah.
That makes sense. Okay. All right.
So I think we wouldn't get too much into
this because you know all the problems
that we have here already.
So firm and user management,
we'll start with kind of firm management.
We've talked before about that kind of
how do we
do the firm 360 flow into Compass?
And then how do we activate the firm?
We don't have the ability to off-board
firms. They live on forever, I think,
today, Candi.
And then how do we manage the firm
relationships?
So we call all of that firm management.
So state of where we actually literally
are,
With starting with firm subscriptions,
so I think I, I think I showed you,
do you remember,
do should I pull up from 360 again? Yeah,
yeah, yeah, we click on the firm,
then it shows the information,
all our codes, yeah,
firm you probably there,
and then at the bottom,
product and services,
not a not a full list, right?
It's got bits and pieces,
most of that is not actually on compass.
So when somebody subscribes to a tax
package, that's through delivery,
like data delivery,
it's not distributed through Compass.
And so the biggest gap today,
because firm subscription,
firm settings in Compass works, right?
You saw the firm settings panel,
there are orientation deficiencies,
but by and large,
If you're talking about the job of being
able to assign a firm and all of the its
user specific things,
we can do that today.
We want to get more into it, actually.
But that synchronization of firm 360 is
obviously not there for the feature level.
So that's the part that's missing.
But if I go just so we can see it with
our eyeballs,
if I kind of go into firm settings,
we know that to manage firm subscriptions,
we list the resources that are available
for us to configure.
We decide what at what level we want to
configure them,
so not all resources are configurable
today, right? You'll see in orders here,
it's a mega list,
but then you can't check is this off.
We want the provisioning of that at a
module level,
so we say we have the ability to define.
the short and height of the firm level
based on.
Is it the module? It is the module, yeah,
and and not the resources themselves.
This is this is the pseudo kind of
feature concept, but once,
as long as you add those resources to a
firm package and I pull up,
this is a rendering of that,
what's in the what's in the contents of
that firm package,
I should be able to configure stuff that.
that I've assigned to that firm, right?
So this firm has an IP package, which, no,
this is the BNI and internal package.
I should have a list of all the features
that are in here.
If I go to a different firm,
what's a good example, actually?
I don't know if we did this actually,
Candi.
I wanna, we're gonna test this out.
I wonder if this dumps data to the other
packages.
Can I try?
This is the test.
I go to a PM. Yeah, in production.
In production. Yeah,
this is one in production. Yeah.
Let's go to, let's go to PVP, I guess.
So this is a PM and I should still see a
very similar list of features, however.
You'll see on here as we go through,
we don't have...
Thank God.
We don't have trade allocations and we
don't have system health events.
That's because we never added those
resources to the PM package.
We only added it to the internal packages
today.
So, I'm gonna go back. So, PVP is like a,
well, actually, it's a,
it's a parent firm, but it's a, it's a PM,
but if I were to kind of provide to N.D.I.
N. So,
each firm type has its own firm type.
Yeah, yeah,
and then just I use the packages,
we got twenty-six,
but here I think we got five or six
different firm packages,
and that's for us to bring certain
features, so you'll see here type,
there's an internal,
there's an introducing broker,
what is this? I don't know.
What is that, Candi? I have uh,
and BNI and internal,
but I also have like the core PM and IB,
uh,
and I think there's IFM and their
Investissements and Manager as well.
I know these types. OK, good. Uh,
with NBIN on the platform, because uh,
like creating a global view is a special
case.
our only our employees have access to
these two firms, BNI and internal,
and BNI and when I go into there,
I'm actually,
we actually have a BNI package that is
targeted for just this kind of loose
definition of a firm, BNI and internal,
and typically we add everything to this.
before we release its client.
So we have access to it, we can test it,
we can see what it looks like,
we make it available to employees before
clients start calling our employees and
asking what the hell this is and can you
support me on it?
And so we do our internal distribution
first by adding stuff to the NBN package
first and the NBN core.
first. We're good. We do our Alpha. Okay,
we're good.
Now we onboard the resources into the
actual client-facing packages.
But as a result of that,
we have an NPI package at the firm level.
We have an internal package, core,
something like that. Yeah,
maybe can you show the core?
So,
the the definition or the biggest
difference, if you search for BNI,
you see core is also an internal type.
Core is the firm ID. Yeah, firm ID. So,
what this one is used for is.
Basically, it got tasks accounts,
and so when we assign a profile in here,
we can mimic what the client can do and
go through.
Yeah.
So this is what we call the test booker
or the if we want to pilot run something,
especially in production,
we'll assign our profile and change our
user package in here.
So then we just like saying like stand
and doing some testing.
with trading.
So they may approve on here and why not
in the BNI and the other one,
the global access firm that Penny was
looking at is that one doesn't have,
first thing is it doesn't have any test
account.
So,
you cannot do the transactional testing
with those,
and secondly is that is some fake firm or
just a firm we make up,
and why do we do that is imagine in the
head office we need someone to...
be able to access all firms and then all
accounts.
But the setup encompasses all firm
contacts fund.
So if you are assigned to IPC,
you can only see the accounts within IPC.
And that is very important because we're
a platform supporting multiple client
firms.
But then we also need someone at the MBIN
headquarter level.
We can access all accounts under the sun.
So we, in the very beginning,
we set up this MBIN, the global SX firm.
And if you think about it,
it's like the parent firm of all our
client firms.
So,
if let's say we have a profile assigned
to this,
we can practically support all the all
the questions,
and you sometimes will see we can select
the firm, yeah, the firm drop down,
Penny Penny showed the firm selector.
because we can go in whichever firm
contacts and then see whatever relevant
to that client. And also this one,
we have to be very careful because again,
it has access to everything and we
primarily use it,
all the features we will put it in there
for sure.
Because the validation,
we have to do a lot of validation,
and if this question we have to jump in,
and so that's why this profile we have
access to everything, yeah,
so those are so in our kind of going back
to our our firm hierarchy.
Yeah, because we didn't talk about this.
So we know that every firm might have its
own broker code,
or it might be belong to a shared broker
code because we were trying to be
economical with the number of broker
codes being used.
And each broker obviously is a business,
right? So for NBI and to Candi's point,
we can't be logging into every single
firm and have like 400 IDs to support
them if I call them.
us it could be any client or client
support team structure is flat.
They'll take calls from any clients,
right? They specialize in like functions.
So like we have a team specializing in
account management,
we have a team specializing in trading,
right?
So they need cross-firm access like to
everything.
So NBN internal is that concept of.
It doesn't actually exist in the
hierarchy.
We made it up to say this is just global
access to all the firms.
So we're careful in provisioning that,
to Kenny's point,
because you can do a lot of damage.
If you're a new guy or uninitiated,
we typically don't give you that access
because you can see all client data,
you can see all transactions,
you can assist in initiating certain
transactions.
from there. But it is a good test bed,
so when we launch new features,
we launch the environment first. Oh, okay.
That's still too much access.
So if you're not supporting a client
directly, because we are not,
the product team isn't,
Raise project team isn't,
we're not client-facing teams,
you don't need access to all those
accounts and all that data.
You just need to know that whatever
feature you deploy.
It works in like for a firm.
So then we have another special case
concept, which is what Candi called out.
It's Coronet. It's Correspondent Network,
which is what BNI was called before BNI.
That's why you see core everywhere.
People hate it.
But this is actually a broker.
So it has a broker code. Okay.
And this is for us to have a dedicated
BNI account range for us to do stuff in.
It's not actually just for testing,
but you know,
if we need to refund somebody or hold
funds or whatever,
we have a set of operational accounts.
that we use that broker code for across
all the teams here,
especially the transactional support
teams,
like accounting might funnel some funds
into there for holding before it goes out
to the firm. You know,
there might be error accounts where, oh,
there's an error,
I need to debit somewhere, it goes,
it passes through those set of accounts.
happens that product team also has a set
of accounts for testing purposes because
production is never the same as UAT.
So we want to have a broker setup with
all the behaviors of a broker in here,
which is called core.
We assign it features just like we do.
here,
so it does have a firm package on its own.
It does have a set of resources that are
assigned to that package,
but specifically tailored to our test
environment and our operational
environment,
and typically also includes all of the
features that BNI and internal would have,
because product team and project teams
would typically use our project.
testing accounts in here,
Stan actually places real orders in our
product team account range.
I actually get a trade confirmation
coming back to say he placed the order
and he better damn well sell it before we
accrue interest because we have to attest
to those accounts.
The use of those accounts for not to make
money but to run operations, right?
So you'll see similar thing,
but just to explain why sometimes you
look in here and you're like, oh,
this package has certain features,
but how come the other firms' packages
don't? Well,
it's because we might not have gone to
that place where we packaged it into the
IBRPM yet, right? So like, yeah,
this is a good example.
I don't think that's.
Oh no, that's not a good example.
Like view system health events is not in
the key in package that you saw. Right.
I don't know where trade allocations went.
Uh, I don't know where it went, um, so...
It kind of works today.
It fulfills the job of the ability to
tailor certain features for certain firms,
the ability to toggle that feature on and
off based on the firm's subscription and
their preference.
So if they have a presence to say,
I don't want to use this tool for my
advisors or my shop,
please turn it off for me.
We will go in here and turn it off for
them. Yeah,
that typically gets addressed when we
launch new features with Radhika. Anyway,
the firm will say, like,
if states got launched,
2 firms didn't want estates,
we turned it off. Actually,
I think we can,
I think we can actually see that.
Is estates in here in, you know?
It still is on tools, no? Oh, it is tools.
So how do we turn them on?
We have to call infinite.
This is why we got to fix the integration.
Yeah, I think, yeah, you can't see,
oh my god, you can't see it on here.
I think it showed, if you throw that,
I saw it.
No, it's not. It's not here. It's shown,
yeah, like this one. Well,
actually a good example that's more
tangible. Yeah, tools. Tools, but yeah,
you can't, you can't show and hide.
These are confusing as well.
It show it in here,
but practically we cannot.
We cannot hide it.
We cannot choose which tool to show.
Yeah,
so I would say limitations here is
strictly like orientation of this forum.
Not everybody comes in here and
understands how it works.
That's the biggest deal we had when we
launched is how do you define the show
and high? Well,
you need to register specific resources.
To do that, and you have to define,
I think, module groups as well,
which is again a very bespoke concept
that somebody came up with to enable the
show and hide.
This is not easy to explain why there are
check boxes in gray. Well,
that's just the way we implemented it.
So there are usability challenges with
this.
Once you train somebody on it, though,
it kind of makes sense.
At least product activation can use it to
launch features. But obviously,
like limitations on degree of control,
how you define the controls and how it
gets loaded into here.
It's just a little confusing. But it like,
I mean, it works.
Yeah, it works. It works to a degree.
You get into tricky things where, like,
if you want something to show up on the
UI,
then you have to define it as a module,
then you have to register these things
separately, even though I say, well,
features wise,
this actually all goes together.
So there is a bit of a limitation on.
Like just the application of resources
itself and how that affects the UI,
but I think Candi can give you more
details on that than I can. No, Owen,
Owen can give you more details on that
than I can call it. Yeah, but like,
there's limitations on, I guess,
the feature bundling.
but not to do with firm settings,
it's more to do with how the resources
are used.
But, for example, this in BNI,
let's consider that it has been
registered in Firm 360 as well. OK,
I remember there we were we were
selecting or subscribing to to some of
the features, and I remember that.
It was it was there as a source of the
route that is going to downstream to to
Compass X because it's where the billing
starts and that's where the firms gets
onboarded in terms of the contract and so
account opening and so forth.
So.
What is a bit confusing for me is that
how we map what has been subscribed here
against what we show here. Yeah. To here.
Yeah. It doesn't map.
That's what I'm saying.
There's no lineage of Fermi 16.
You said that it's totally offline.
It's totally.
Manual, yeah, every, but OK.
It's.
Somehow, for example, here says, okay,
this firm has subscribed to trading.
How we can see that,
whether you don't see it, you're gonna,
it's totally offline, two points of entry,
right? So, when you first onboard a firm,
we have a team called Firm
Implementations. They call the firm,
the key contract at the firm, and say,
"I'm now gonna set up all the systems and
tools and services."
for you.
That person called Kayla is going to take
down and look at the contract and take
down, okay, what is this,
what is this firm supposed to have?
And then she's going to go into each of,
because she's got a procedure guy,
she's going to go into each of the
systems and configure it based on that.
playbook based on that set of procedures.
And one of the things she will do is she
will go into Compass and she will do the
checks right on what the firm is supposed
to have.
And if the firm at the time of onboarding
says, oh,
I'm going to bring my own account opening
solution because that's the most real,
like nobody says don't take trading.
Like they usually say I'm bringing in my
own account opening solution.
Then Kayla would go into here and just
hide it.
What ideally Kayla should have is a
one-step setup,
which is what we're seeing here,
from configuration,
so the information doesn't get lost and
it's traceable.
And we take this information and we use
whatever is relevant for Compass and we
implement it.
That's where we want to be.
But clearly that does not exist today.
So again, it's all manual.
And we don't onboard too many firms a
month. Right? What a year, in a year?
I mean, like, I don't know,
like the half dozen dozen firms.
And so we get away, but.
The with the manual communication,
and then if there's confusion,
Kayla just kind of walks over fast,
but it is disconnected,
and so when you kind of come back to here,
and like Ray said before,
if you want a global view of all the
products and services for a firm,
you're going to pull it from different
places.
To Put into here.
on the insights, right?
And he will have the whole thing going on
with data aggregation and analytics and
adoption metrics and all that stuff for
that firm from all the different places
that you need to pull that information
from because it's not centralized.
So yeah, so it's kind of segregated.
It depends on the.
So that's one entry point.
The other entry point is when we launch a
new feature,
then Radhika goes out to all the firms
and says, it's like, you know, well,
number one,
we're going to determine should that firm
have this feature or not is even relevant
for them. Check.
And then the other piece is have we like,
you know,
Has has has the kind of heavy like RVPs
or however like have they signed a
contract and defined it?
Is it relevant for them when we launch
that product? Who does it go to?
Who actually signed this contract? So,
that's kind of like the digit
implementation with Wilson.
We know that as well,
and then we go again and...
kind of come into it and manually
configure companies in a certain way to
distribute that feature to the firm.
Usually the stuff that goes to this team,
all of it is core anyway,
like core product.
So everybody tends to get it and
Radhika's team's job mainly is to refine,
okay, even though you should have it,
do you want it?
And then you get that feedback from the
clients and then we go on.
Cascade that into a firm setting.
Still kind of conversation.
Ideally.
firms actually have a version of firm
settings, right? And so when we say, hey,
this feature is now available,
you can have it,
you can share it with your users,
then a firm can decide at the firm level,
do I want to hide it globally for
everybody or show it?
Both the ones that obviously gets
distributed to you.
It doesn't remove the step of firm
implementation or product activation
coming in and say,
now I'm going to assign this feature to
that firm. They still need to do that,
but a firm ideally actually sees a
version of that and then refines the
preferences of what they want to globally
set in the system for their own users
that way. Right now,
it's all through calls, emails, feedback,
what do you want, what do you not want,
I'll do it for you, that kind of thing.
Um...
Or in most cases,
we actually only do that for like the top
five firms, everybody else.
Just gonna enable it to hell with it,
right? Just gonna get it,
stop asking questions.
So, when we deliver a new feature,
do we have some kind of like product road
show, for example,
invite all of the parties and or record a
webinar or something like that to go
through presentation and.
Not formally,
we've been talking about it for years,
but nobody has time to put one together.
So we used to have annual conferences,
that's where we showcase our features.
And then that's kind of our main touch
point with clients to find out what's new
and upcoming.
But we've actually pivoted the format of
our annual client conference.
as of this year.
So it's no longer an BNI conference,
it's more of an industry conference.
So now there is actually a whole of,
we used to do all the product marketing
and kind of engagement in that conference.
We disinvited half those people because
we wanted to bring more C-suite attendees
to our industry conference.
Now where are these people going to go?
So next year there should be a roadshow.
But somebody just needs to plan it.
And I think Radhika has spearheaded that.
In lieu of that,
then it's a lot of communication and
collateral.
And so the go-to-market process does
include product marketing.
That's what Yash is here for.
There's still written communications,
notice, maybe change management,
learning and development comes in and
runs sessions,
run webinars to introduce the feature.
People do show up to that.
to learn about the new features,
especially if they're big features and
people,
we get quite good attendance on the big
ones.
And then we have a handful of what we
call the special handling firms where we
drive a direct engagement with them to
talk them through the planning and what
they're getting and do you want it or not?
And they can have the opportunity to kind
of customize your experience.
Give us feature requests, uh,
because those are our biggest clients. OK,
yeah, yeah.
I don't think,
I think this section for add-on has been
abandoned. Nobody uses it.
I don't know why it was there.
Do you know why it was there?
Yeah,
there was an ambition to put it on there.
Okay, so launched. Just ignore it.
I don't even know how you would populate
something here. No, no. No, I do.
One thing to note, I guess, Candi,
do we still have the concept of active
firm activation?
Like if we have a new firm coming in from
Firm 360.
What's the status of it on here?
So you see this is the list of all the
firms we pull from Firm 360 and the
downloads done every day.
So if someone set up, like Penny said,
plan implementation,
basically they interact with Firm 360.
if they want to onboard a firm or do any
changes. And in some situation,
maybe a firm got expanded.
So they got more Oracle, more ranges,
or maybe the account ranges for them.
Anything changed on the firm level.
So this loaded job.
will pick up the changes or any net new
firm rather than to BNI and load it in
here. So these ones not just enable,
you see a lot of them are enabled,
but there's also maybe something disabled
at the meantime.
And so the firm onboarding process for us
is.
When the firm got set up in Firm 360,
then someone will have to come here.
Usually, it was digital support,
not sure to them. Yeah,
they would come here,
they got the message that we have to
onboard the firm. No,
it's firm activation, product activation.
It's Radhika Stanley.
Is it? I don't know,
like between the three teams that keeps...
Ohh, yeah, I'm not sure,
but they they will come here, find a firm,
and if the firm usually the first time
the firm can you find a disabled firm?
It's hard to find, doesn't that exist?
Hmm, yeah, yeah, OK, yeah,
if you bring it up, can you click on that,
please? Yeah.
So, you see, um, are you in the front?
Yeah, firm setting. Oh, yeah, yeah.
So it doesn't, yeah,
so this is the default,
but then you got a choice here to enable
the firm.
So the firm currently is disabled.
So what they do is they have to,
they got some agreement what the firm
wants, so the show and time.
So they have to change the usability and
then enable the firm.
But that's the only thing they do because
everything else presets.
Even in here you see these features is
coming from the firm package.
And the firm package, as we said,
it's by the firm tech.
So when you load the firm,
it knows the firm type,
so it will pre-fill the firm,
pick up the firm package template,
and then load the features in here.
But then the activation team's job is to
make sure if the firm say,
I want to about onboarding,
I have my own onboarding solution.
So,
then they would hide the onboarding
module here, and that's it,
and then enable the firm. So, the sorry,
so let's describe like the enable firm.
What is that actually do? Does it one,
of course,
it changes the status to active,
but I think...
I want to show one.
If you click on user on the left, yeah,
so you see one condition is we always
onboard the firm,
enable the firm 1st and then you add
users. So if you haven't done that,
you are blocked from updating any user.
And the reason is, as we said,
when you provision the user account,
it also have to reference what your firm
has.
And so that's why the firm setting has to
be done first,
and then we allow you to set up users.
Yeah, that's, yeah.
So that's the difference. Yeah, yeah.
Get out and keep. Yeah,
I'll be in box and I don't know what
these people are.
OK,
I think I think that's all I wanted to go
through anyway for from settings.
So maybe I'll change,
or you can change the colors on this.
Like, this is gray, it doesn't exist.
We talked about this,
this actually exists.
Firm offboarding does not exist.
Once you enable a firm,
we can't disable a firm, can we?
I think we can, yeah. Oh, nice. Yes,
if you can.
Well, we don't anything,
it's just disabled.
And I don't want to randomly disable from,
yeah,
just so bring a bathroom any enable from.
Do to ourselves, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
and then I think that's a go to firm
settings, yeah, ohh, you don't,
I don't think, I don't think it works,
I don't think we scoped it in, OK, sorry,
it was getting too close to launch at the
time,
and we said we save some time enough to
do the disabling, yeah,
'cause the disabling.
Flag on the yeah, no,
'cause then the team got into the debate
of, ohh, Penny, and once you disable,
like,
how long do you retain that firm
information for and all its users,
and when do you purge and when do you
delete, and I'm like,
I don't wanna talk about that,
and they don't do disabling because even
the firm left us.
Yeah,
we're obligated to keep the history for,
for how long first? Exactly, yeah.
So then there's no real, no material,
like, yeah, purpose. It is,
but you have to be, yeah,
why do you ask about the line, because...
It is, well,
maybe I decide two years later to delete
it.
It's gonna be a kind of offline
operations,
script maintenance thing to delete them.
I don't think,
but they don't they don't create a
scheduled job.
I don't think they create a scheduled job,
but what's the policy,
and then if there isn't one,
what's the purpose?
People,
like if you present an option to somebody,
you have to tell them what it's for.
And then like if you don't have,
like if there's no need for it right now,
the firm can sit on there forever.
It disappears.
I don't even think it disappears off Firm
360.
And so if we're supposed to be a
representation of Firm 360,
there's no disabling in Firm 360 either.
So representing it disabling means you're
just shutting off the ability to create
users. It came from Firm 360.
If it's disabled in Firm 360,
it will send down. Oh, is it?
Because we download the status.
So we don't even,
so we can't even disable on the platform
because it might still be active in Firm
360. Yeah, yeah,
I think there's some complication because.
..
We have to synchronize from Phone 360 and
I don't remember because we don't offer
so often. Yeah,
last time we offer someone,
we still have to keep the data in the
system for all the purposes and some of
our MBI and stuff,
they will have still have to go into
those accounts. Is it settled?
So that's why you cannot.
Disabled it from yet. OK, yeah, yeah,
that's a better reason in my case. Yeah,
yeah, yeah,
like I I questioned one time H.S.B.C.
that still exists, yeah,
'cause their accounts have to live on and
someone has access to those accounts.
Someone has to access,
'cause they're trying to close out the
accounts and move the assets over to Rdsp,
yeah.
That's much fun, actually. Yeah, yeah.
I didn't want to get into any of that,
so I'm like, ***** it!" Yeah,
it can deals, yeah.
As soon as you create in Firm 360,
so it takes time to set up,
so it means that you create,
you can state a new state.
pending and as soon as you set up you can
enable but
When the in the firm 360 gets disabled,
so it should be replicated here in
Compass X that it's been disabled,
but in terms of the data governance,
this one throw it in our book,
but then we have an enable it in Compass.
So, that's why is in this firm selector,
but if a firm I don't even know.
It did happen ever.
So change your firm to inactive in from
360. It doesn't happen that often. Sorry,
Ali, cut you off too. So I don't know.
But, anyway, it doesn't, it doesn't work.
to keep them in the book.
I guess that's why.
So, it's not, it's not matching,
but it could be one of two reasons,
because the loader would filter out
active firms only and then low income
books, so I, I,
I don't remember the disabled firm. Yeah,
if the firm became inactive income in
from 360, does it do anything?
I think it does something,
but if you filter them out,
then what is it?
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah,
the other way around. So this one active,
so it got load into campus,
but product activation hasn't turned it
on. So the status on campus is disabled.
We think. Yeah, yes.
But we can verify that. Yeah,
like this whole disabling is such a low
priority.
No, this firm is active. Yeah,
it is active on here,
but it's not active in here.
Well, I don't think we care about that.
No,
it's not active in here because we
haven't turned on the firm settings for
them.
And the reason could be we haven't
onboard them to the MBI and business.
Or there's an interpretation.
Or they don't use compass or they don't
haven't provide any user for us to set up.
Maybe.
confirm that. Radhika? Yeah, I guess so.
You really want to know? Well,
just for educational purposes,
because we clearly have thought very
little about this deactivation concept,
that it's just whatever was at the time
of interpretation.
But I guess my, I still,
I'm still kind of,
I'm still just in terms of like the
availability of this,
it's just not a focus.
It's not that important. Yeah.
If we, if,
if there was a security thing like user
deactivation exists, for sure,
like I mean,
that is just employee leaves a firm,
you wanna immediately deactivate the user
and eliminate access.
There's a clear security use case for it.
Firm deactivation, like, yeah,
as long as you have no user,
that's no breaking, like, yeah, who cares?
Well, like, it's more when you get the...
Firm disabled in compass X,
I think the underlying users no longer
can do anything, is that right?
I think so, Candi.
I will,
because you guys do this as a homework
investigation, then we got no idea.
With you showing me if firm was disabled,
and there were no users under that,
so it's logical because it's inheriting
the firm packages.
but make no assumptions, Ali.
In this current platform environment,
we made a lot of horrible decisions,
or in this case, really,
we really didn't spend time on it.
We said, okay,
I said lifecycle management.
So this firm management should be firm
lifecycle management,
which goes from subscription to
activation to maintenance to deactivation.
When we got to deactivation, I think,
was it just me and you at the time, Candi,
or is it somebody else?
I can't remember who was responsible for
this at the time. We just said,
forget about it. We're going to move on.
That's all.
And then so I think the dev team did some
stuff.
To interpret what he, what do you do,
and that's why I think it's still worth.
I think we, we, we, yeah, we scoped it,
and then,
but then you can't fully descope
something if you get it.
So, in the code, when the user,
for example,
is under a firm that is disabled,
because when they need to check the
intersection of the firm package and user
package, okay, when they log in,
and then if...
Affirm package status.
Is disable.
Which I don't know whether they have this,
yeah, but it's no,
it's but it's not the firm package status,
it's a firm attribute, yes, yeah,
it's a firm status in Compass,
which has no ties to Okta.
Remember, right? Like,
so user authentication, like,
that's the part I'm not,
I think Katie's gonna now find out.
We should probably find out. I don't,
we don't know if it blocks, like,
I don't know if there's like a validation
when you get to Okta to say that is this
from active or not. I'm not sure.